Guide to the Robert Branner papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Medieval Manuscript Research Materials, 1965-1973, undated
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Fr. 17229 undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Fr. 20120 undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Fr. 22969 undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Fr. 24404 undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Fr. 24429 undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Nouv. acq. fr. 1098, 1966-1969, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Nouv. acq. fr. 10128 undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Nouv. acq. fr. 23686 undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin II, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 32, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 33, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 36, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 77, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 167, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 203, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 212 C, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 226, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 228, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 233, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 233 A, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 660, 1970-1973, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 796, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 824, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 830, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 862, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 976, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1022, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1023, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1073 A, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1075, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1077, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1107, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1112, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 1246, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 2235, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 2438, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 5111, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 6191, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 8865, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 8884, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 8923, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 9402, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 9441, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 9455, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 10426 undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 10434 undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 10489 1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 10525 undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 10593 undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11521 undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11534 and 11535 1967, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11536 undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11538 undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11539 undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11543 undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11549 1967, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11560 1985-1986, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11560 -- Moralized Bible, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11565 1967, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11704 undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 11930 and 11931 undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12054 undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12059 undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12066 undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12068 undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12083 undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12593 undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12614 undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12833 undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12834 undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 12953 undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 13142 undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 13144 undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 13247 undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 13234-14237 undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 14266-14267 undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 14397 undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 14452 undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 14860 undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15185 undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15237 undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15467 undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15475 undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15477 undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15510 undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15613 undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15615 undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 15616 1969, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16200 undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16260 undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16272 undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16541 undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16743-16746 undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16747 undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16719-16720 undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16748 undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16824 undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 16843 undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 17318-17319 undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 17326 1970, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 17439 undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 17907 undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 18224 undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Latin 18357 undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- N.a.l. 406, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- N.a.l. 1359, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- N.a.l. 1392, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- N.a.l. 1509, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Paris -- Nationale -- Picardie 165, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Paris -- Musée Carnavalet, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 12, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 90, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 394, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 609, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 1180, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 1181, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 1185, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 1273, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Paris -- Ste. Geneviève -- 2689-2690, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Pécs (Hungary), undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Perugia, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Philadelphia -- Free Library, 1966-1971, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Philadelphia -- Museum of Art, 1971, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Princeton, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Provins, 1972, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Reading, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Reims, 1965-1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Rome, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Rouen -- Bibliothèque Municipale -- 3016, 1965-1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Rouen -- Bibliothèque Municipale -- Bible, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Rouen -- Bibliothèque Municipale -- Missal, 1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - St. Etienne, 1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - St. Florian (Austria) 1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - St. Omer, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - St. Paul im Lavanttal, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - San Marino, 1970-1972, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Sarnen, 1970, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Sens, 1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Soissons, 1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Stuttgart, 1967, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Tours, 1967, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Toledo, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Troyes -- Bibliothèque -- 33, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Troyes -- Bibliothèque -- 103, 1967, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Troyes -- Bibliothèque -- 170, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Troyes -- Bibliothèque -- 392, 1968-1971, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Valencien, 1965, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Vatican, 1968, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Venice, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 112, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 1144, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 1150, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 1179, 1967-1971, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 1241, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 1904, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 2374, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Vienna -- Österreich National Bibliothek -- 2611, 1967, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Warsaw, 1970-1972, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Washington 1970, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Wilhering (Austria), 1967, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Williamstown, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Winchester, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Wixom (Mr. and Mrs. William) Collection, 1967-1971, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Wolfenbüttel, 1970, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Zwettl (Austria), undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Location unknown -- General, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Location unknown -- Adamson, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Location unknown -- Beatty, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Location unknown -- Berès, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Location unknown -- Breslauer, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Location unknown -- Burkitt, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Location unknown -- Didot, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Location unknown -- Gilhofer, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Location unknown -- Kraus, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Location unknown -- Maggs, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Location unknown -- Mostyn, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Location unknown -- Olschki, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Location unknown -- Perrins, Dyson 32, 1968-1969, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Location unknown -- Quaritsch, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Location unknown -- Sotheby Sales, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Location unknown -- Willoughby Psalter, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)